Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America Memorabilia 5030 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America Memorabilia
1914-1961
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America (BRSA)
5030 MB
0.58 cubic feet
0.6 linear ft.
Memorabilia.
Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America Memorabilia including badges, paperwork, railroad passes, membership cards, tie clips, cuff links, railroad tokens and membership push pins.
5930704
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 15, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5030: U.S. Emergency Board No. 179 Exhibits and Related Material
Implements, utensils, etc.; Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America; Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company; Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen; Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen --Collectibles; Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America; Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America --Collectibles; Central Michigan Railroad; Chicago Transit Authority; Erie Railroad Company; New York Central Railroad Company
5930704
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen (of America) - Badges, 1950-1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  3 (1950, 1956, 1961)
- Brotherhood of Signalmen of America - Patch and Badges, 1938-1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  1 patch and 3 badges (1938, 1952, 1958)
- Brotherhood of Signalmen of America - Misc. paperwork, 1914-1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Railroad passes - [New York Central Railroad Company; Erie Railroad Company; Baltimore and Ohio], 1936-1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  ranging from 1936-1961 (one appears to be dated 1868)
- Michigan Central Railroad - Watch inspection, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Membership cards and railroad pass, 1944-1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Seal - Michigan Central RR System (Box 1, Folder 7)
  BRS of A, Affiliated with AFL Seal of General Chairman -- Hand held Sealmaker belonging to the Michigan Central Railroad, seal imprint lettering - "Michigan Central Railroad System B.R.S. of A., Seal of General Chairman"
- Tie clip with gold railroad engine on it (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Cuff link with gold railroad engine on it (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Cuff link with gold railroad engine on it (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Tie clip with railroad engine on it (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Cuff link with railroad engine on it (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Cuff link with railroad engine on it (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Tie clip with silver and blue railroad engine on it (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Cuff links (2) with silver and blue railroad engine on them (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Tie clips - 1-silver with WJD lettering on it; 2-Engine and car 'Empire Note Express, 999' (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Tie clip - black railroad engine with red wheels on it (Box 2, Folder 10)
- cuff link - black railroad engine with red wheels on it (Box 2, Folder 11)
- cuff link - black railroad engine with red wheels on it (Box 2, Folder 12)
- A miniature gold wrench - 'To commemorate your golden anniversary, a golden wrench from General Railway Signal Company' (Box 2, Folder 13)
- 2 Railroad tokens - 1-Surface CTA; 2-Pioneer Association (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Push pin - Continuous Membership, 25 years - BRS of A; Key chain - Southern District Winner 1956, Safety Award (Box 2, Folder 15)